(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-01T01:59:26.435637",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
え、皆様、本日は轟はじめ初単独生誕祭2025にお越しくださいまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Um, everyone, thank you so much for attending Todoroki Hajime's First Solo Birthday Live 2025 today!
開催に先立ちまして、皆様にお願いとご案内を申し上げます。
Ahead of the event, we have a few requests and announcements for everyone.
当配信は一部収録を含みますが、生配信部分もございますので、いっぱいコメントして盛り上げてください。
This broadcast includes some pre-recorded segments, but there are also live portions, so please comment a lot and hype it up!
周りも見えているんですが…
We can see around us too, but...
うんと、うんと、パソコン…きょう…きっちゃ！おお！きっちゃ！
Um, um, PC... kyo... kiccha! Oh! Kiccha!
あはははは、緊張しちゃった！ありがとうございます。
Ahahaha, I got so nervous! Thank you very much.
え、テレビやパソコン、スマホの前での飲食は可能ですが、
Eating and drinking in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone is allowed,
キーボードにこぼさないようにお気をつけください。
but please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
え、当配信のハッシュタグは、
The hashtag for this broadcast is...
轟はじめ初単独生誕祭2025です。SNSでたくさんポストしてください！
#TodorokiHajimeBirthdayLive2025. Please post a lot on SNS!
え、会期中、パソコンやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影、
Also, taking photos with PCs or smartphones during the event—
え、皆様、本日は轟はじめ初単独生誕祭2025にお越しくださいまして、誠にありがとうございます。
Um, everyone, thank you so much for attending Todoroki Hajime's First Solo Birthday Live 2025 today!
開催に先立ちまして、皆様にお願いとご案内を申し上げます。
Ahead of the event, we have a few requests and announcements for everyone.
当配信は一部収録を含みますが、生配信部分もございますので、いっぱいコメントして盛り上げてください。
This broadcast includes some pre-recorded segments, but there are also live portions, so please comment a lot and hype it up!
ではでは、2周目確かルール。わくわく、2回目、2回目言ってもありがとね。
Now then, second lap, checking the rules. Exciting, even if I say it a second time, thanks!
テレビやパソコン、スマートフォンの前での飲食は可能ですが、キーボードにこぼさないようにお気をつけください。
Eating and drinking in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone is allowed, but please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
当配信のハッシュタグは轟はじめ初単独生誕祭2025です。SNSでたくさんポストしてください！
The hashtag for this broadcast is #TodorokiHajimeBirthdayLive2025. Please post a lot on SNS!
会期中、パソコンやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影、大歓迎です！たくさんポストして盛り上げてくれると嬉しいです！
Taking photos with PCs or smartphones during the event is very welcome! We'd be so happy if you post a lot and hype it up!
それでは、開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Now then, please wait a little longer until the show starts.
下手うっすら ban
With no luck, ban
謝っても無駄
Even apologizing is useless
何がしたいか分からん
I have no idea what you want to do
もううんざりだ
I'm already fed up
馬鹿ばっかだ全く
Completely full of idiots
呻呼 生き苦しい世界だわ
Groaning, it's a hard world to live in
1.2.3. からカウンター
From 1, 2, 3, counter
シャイなバーテンゾンビに頼んだ
I asked the shy bartender zombie
まやかしか妖脳汁ビア
Illusory goblin-juice beer
天然モノです微炭酸
It's natural, lightly carbonated
暴れる準備は決まって
The preparation to rampage is set
派手なイントロダクション頷った
Nodding to the flashy introduction
夢のパーティーが始まりだ
The dream party is beginning
あっかんべーのべーまた ban ban ban
Making a face, again, ban ban ban
五月雨鬱陶しいなもうアイアイアイアイヤ
It's so annoying, hey ay ay ay ay-ya
あっかんべーのべーまた ban ban ban
Making a face, again, ban ban ban
金環際関わんなよダルいだけ
Don't get involved, it's just a drag
揺れる揺れる swinging
Swaying, swaying, swinging
圧倒的だな singing
It's overwhelming singing
まだまだ踊ってよござんしょ
Keep dancing, won't you?
揺れる揺れる swinging
Swaying, swaying, swinging
圧倒的だな singing
It's overwhelming singing
タラッタッタ タラッタッタ
Tarattatta tarattatta
「 清廉潔白 私 の 過去 に は 何 の 過ち も 御座い ませ ん 」
"My past is pure and spotless, without any mistakes."
分厚くなってくルールブック
The rulebook is getting thicker
見逃した時には万事休す
When you miss it, it's all over
びっくり精度のサーチライト
A searchlight with surprising precision
「 それ は やばい よ 、 、 」 が 1 番 怖い よ
"That's dangerous..." is the scariest part
レッド も イエロー も 関係 ない の よ
Red and yellow don't matter at all
一発退場 「 はい ！ お疲れ様 」
One-strike expulsion, "Yes! Good job."
1.2.3 から カウンター
From 1, 2, 3, counter
熱い ロックンロール を 食らった
Took a hit of hot rock 'n' roll
インター ルード に 逆上せる ヴィラン
A villain getting carried away in the interlude
バンギャ の ゾンビ も パラッパー
Bangya zombies too, parappa
アイドルタイム も 終わって
Idol time is over too
あっ と 言う 間 に こっ から 終盤 だ ぞ
Before you know it, it's the climax from here
ゾンビ も 猫 も 三蔵法師 も 踊る だけ
Zombies, cats, and Xuanzang Sanzang just dance
あっかんべーのべーまた ban ban ban
Making a face, again, ban ban ban
五月雨鬱陶しいなもうアイアイアイアイヤ
It's so annoying, hey ay ay ay ay-ya
あっかんべーのべーまた ban ban ban
Making a face, again, ban ban ban
金環際関わんなよダルいだけ
Don't get involved, it's just a drag
揺れる揺れる swinging
Swaying, swaying, swinging
圧倒的だな singing
It's overwhelming singing
まだまだ踊ってよござんしょ
Keep dancing, won't you?
揺れる揺れる swinging
Swaying, swaying, swinging
圧倒的だな singing
It's overwhelming singing
タラッタッタ タラッタッタ
Tarattatta tarattatta
あっかんべーのべーまた ban ban ban
Making a face, again, ban ban ban
五月雨鬱陶しいなもうアイアイアイアイヤ
It's so annoying, hey ay ay ay ay-ya
あっかんべーのべーまた ban ban ban
Making a face, again, ban ban ban
金環際関わんなよダルいだけ
Don't get involved, it's just a drag
揺れる揺れる swinging
Swaying, swaying, swinging
圧倒的だな singing
It's overwhelming singing
まだまだ踊ってよござんしょ
Keep dancing, won't you?
揺れる揺れる swinging
Swaying, swaying, swinging
圧倒的だな singing
It's overwhelming singing
タラッタッタ タラッタッタ
Tarattatta tarattatta
あっかんべーのべーまた ban ban ban
Making a face, again, ban ban ban
五月雨鬱陶しいなもうアイアイアイアイヤ
It's so annoying, hey ay ay ay ay-ya
あっかんべーのべーまた ban ban ban
Making a face, again, ban ban ban
金環際関わんなよダルいだけ
Don't get involved, it's just a drag
揺れる揺れる swinging
Swaying, swaying, swinging
圧倒的だな singing
It's overwhelming singing
まだまだ踊ってよござんしょ
Keep dancing, won't you?
揺れる揺れる swinging
Swaying, swaying, swinging
圧倒的だな singing
It's overwhelming singing
タラッタッタ タラッタッタ
Tarattatta tarattatta
あっかんべーのべーまた ban ban ban
Making a face, again, ban ban ban
五月雨鬱陶しいなもうアイアイアイアイヤ
It's so annoying, hey ay ay ay ay-ya
あっかんべーのべーまた ban ban ban
Making a face, again, ban ban ban
金環際関わんなよダルいだけ
Don't get involved, it's just a drag
まだまだ終わるか ban ban ban しないで
Don't end yet with ban ban ban!
なんだか忙しく笑うタウン
A town laughing busily for some reason
街中バラバラ
The whole town is scattered
暴れたゾンビとロックスター
Raging zombies and rock stars
と飛んでいくシガレット
And cigarettes flying away
空から撃ち抜くバニーガール
A bunny girl shooting from the sky
騒いでる様々
Various things making noise
現れた近所のバランスァー
The neighborhood balancer has appeared
笑ったガキんちょとスーサイド
A laughing kid and suicide
この惨状辿って
Following this tragedy
まだまだ行けるか
Can we still keep going?
ハッピーエンドのチャイムが
If the happy ending chime
想像通りじゃないなら
Isn't what we imagined
塗り替えてしまうのさ
We'll repaint it
ゆらゆらゆらゆらゆらゆら
Swinging, swinging, swinging
愛を謳うとは
Singing about love
分かり合うものではないから
Doesn't mean we have to understand each other
蹴飛ばし染め上げてごらん
Kick it and dye it, go ahead
そんなもんさ
That's just how it is
なんか忙しく笑うタウン
The town is busy and laughing for some reason
街中バラバラ
In the middle of the city, scattered around
暴れたゾンビとロックスター
Zombies and rock stars are causing a ruckus
と飛んでくシガレット
Cigarettes are flying through the air
空から撃ち抜くバニーガール
A bunny girl shoots from the sky
騒いでいる様々
Various things are making noise
現れた近所のバランスー
The neighborhood balancer appears
笑ったガキんちょとスーサイド
A laughing kid and a suicide
この惨状辿って
Following this tragedy
まだまだ行けるか
Can we still keep going?
ハッピーエンドのチャイムが
If the happy ending chime
想像通りじゃないなら
Isn’t what we imagined
塗り替えてしまうのさ
We’ll repaint it
ゆらゆらゆらゆらゆら
Swinging, swinging, swinging, swinging, swinging
愛を謳うとは
Singing about love
分かり合うものではないから
Doesn’t mean we have to share it
蹴飛ばし染め上げてごらん
Kick it and dye it, go ahead
そんなもんさ
That’s just how it is
正直こんなの 意味あるのかって
Honestly, is any of this meaningful?
考えたところで堂々巡りで
It’s just going around in circles
あれもこれもそれも気になる気になる気になる
I’m interested in this and that, and everything
ああ
Ah
それぞれ願う正義が絡み合う
Everyone’s desired justice is intertwined
咳嗽 まだまだ行けそう
Ah, we can still keep going
ハッピーエンドのチャイムが
If the happy ending chime
想像通りじゃないなら
Isn’t what we imagined
塗り替えてしまうのさ
We’ll repaint it
ゆらゆらゆらゆらゆら どうぞ
Swinging, swinging, swinging, swinging, swinging, go on
愛を謳うとは
Singing about love
分かり合うものではないから
Doesn’t mean we have to share it
蹴飛ばし染め上げてごらん
Kick it and dye it, go ahead
そんなもんさ
That’s just how it is
ハッピーエンドのチャイムが
If the happy ending chime
想像通りじゃないなら
Isn’t what we imagined
塗り替えてしまうのさ
We’ll repaint it
ゆらゆらゆらゆらゆら どうぞ
Swinging, swinging, swinging, swinging, swinging, go on
愛を謳うとは
Singing about love
分かり合うものではないから
Doesn’t mean we have to share it
蹴飛ばし染め上げてごらん
Kick it and dye it, go ahead
そんなもんさ
That’s just how it is
どこで何が起きるか分からない
We don’t know where or when something will happen
まだやり直せるかな
Can we still start over?
ハッピーエンドのチャイムが
If the happy ending chime
想像通りじゃないなら
Isn’t what we imagined
塗り替えてしまうのさ
We’ll repaint it
ゆらゆらゆらゆらゆら どうぞ
Swinging, swinging, swinging, swinging, swinging, go on
愛を謳うとは
Singing about love
分かり合うものではないから
Doesn’t mean we have to share it
蹴飛ばし染め上げてごらん
Kick it and dye it, go ahead
そんなもんさ
That’s just how it is
ハッピーエンドのチャイムが
If the happy ending chime
想像通りじゃないなら
Isn’t what we imagined
塗り替えてしまうのさ
We’ll repaint it
ゆらゆらゆらゆらゆら どうぞ
Swinging, swinging, swinging, swinging, swinging, go on
愛を謳うとは
Singing about love
分かり合うものではないから
Doesn’t mean we have to share it
蹴飛ばし染め上げてごらん
Kick it and dye it, go ahead
そんなもんさ
That’s just how it is
はふ、ふぅ…
Hah, phew...
みなさん！
Everyone!
こんちかー！
Konchika!
初めてのチェータンチェイ来てくれて、ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming to my very first birthday live!
本日は、チュドキはじめチェータンチェイ2025です！
Today is the Hiodoshi Ao Birthday Live 2025!
特典、ポチスタしぐと嬉しい？あんよ、超レンド入ってるよ？いい？
Special bonuses, did you get the postcard set?
ありがとうございまーす！嬉しい！
Thank you so much! I'm so happy!
本調子で、あんよちこい！いろんな初めて驚きするので、
Stay in top form and follow along!
ぜひポチスタしてくれると嬉しい、嬉しい！
There are lots of surprising firsts, so I'd be so happy if you push-to-start!
え、さきほどは、カミカゼとオフサイドという曲を聞いていただきました。
Um, earlier, you heard the songs Kamikaze and offside.
どうですか？
How was it?
かっこよかったですか？
Was it cool?
かっこよかったよー！
It was cool!
ありがとう、ありがとう！
Thank you, thank you!
ね、最初の曲もね、この振り付けもめちゃくちゃ大好きなの で、めちゃくちゃ披露できてうれしいです！
You know, I love the first song and its choreography so much, so I'm so happy to be able to perform it!
このあとも、まだたくさんあるので、一緒に楽しんでください！
There's still a lot more coming up after this, so please enjoy it together!
次は、今かっこよかったけど、とっておきパートでしゅう。
Next up, even though that was cool, it's a special treat part.
おー、それでは、いきましょう！
Oh, well then, let's go!
アップダウンは世の常
Rising and falling is pretty normal in this world
クズ引いたって動かない
Even if I draw a bad hand, I won't let it show
肝心なのは Strong な Mind
It's very important to have a strong mind
出し抜いて Survive
Outsmart them and survive
行き着く先は Heaven or hell
Are we heading to heaven or hell?
この世界のルール
This world has only one rule
たった一つ 勝者こそが正義
The winner is always right
女は度胸
Being a woman is all about guts
焦れさせるのアイツを
I'm gonna keep him guessing
やれることなんたってやる
I'll do anything I have to
あたしは賭けづまりのクイーン
I'm a compulsive gambling queen
見通そうぜ You doubt me
I can see right through you, you doubt me
読み切って レッツ Showdown
Reading all the signs, let's have a showdown
Deal with the devil
見透かして あたしのものにする
I'll see right through you and make you all mine
あなたの髪の毛一本まで全部
Down to the very last hair on your head
A million dollars I'd say raise
震えているのさ 坊や
I'm simply trembling, my boy
降ろしはしないさ
I won't let you drop out
Deal with the devil
Uhhhnn 興奮
Uhn, what an excitement
たまらないわ スリル
I can't have enough of this thrill
誰にも触らせない この Money
I won't let anyone touch this money
A million dollars I'd say raise
さあ Com'on 覚悟決めて
So come on and make up your mind
震え高鳴る My heart
Tremble and go wild, my heart
欲しがるようにね まだ ベイビー
It's a secret, but...
誰にも負けない
I won't lose to anyone
感じさせて Love me honey
Let me feel it, love me honey
覚悟を決めて
Make up your mind,
震えてるわマイハート
Trembling, my heart,
欲しがる 容赦ねぇ
Craving with no mercy,
まだベイビー
Still a baby,
誰にも負けない 感じさせて
Making me feel like I won't lose to anyone,
ラブミーハニー
Love me, honey
あんなちゃちい勝負は
Such cheap parlor tricks
ほら見せてあげる
I'll show you right now
秘密って甘いの
Secrets are so sweet
仕掛けて罠に嵌めるわ
Setting a trap to catch you
油断誘うのよ
Luring your carelessness
思考を止めたらジエンド
If you stop thinking, it's the end
何も知らないような顔で落とすわ
Bringing you down with an innocent face
虚勢でしょ それ you doubt me
You're bluffing, right? You doubt me
読み切って レッツ showdown
Reading it through, let's showdown
deal with the devil
見透かして
See right through you
どんな小さなずるだって
No matter how small the cheat is
あたしの目はごまかせないわ
You can't fool my eyes
a million dollars i'd say raise
刈り取った相手は骨まで
I'll take you down to the bone
愛し尽くしてあげる
And love you to exhaustion
狙った獲物は逃さない
I won't let my prey escape
唇濡らしていただくわ my babe
Wetting my lips before I take you, my babe
ダイヤのジャックで手数が揃うわ
With the jack of diamonds, my hand is complete
笑顔を待つだけ
Killing my smile and waiting
あたしのポーカーフェイスは it's perfect
My poker face is it's perfect
一部の隙も見せたりしないわ
I won't show a single opening
視線感じているわ
I'm feeling your gaze
おののきは最後まで
The trembling goes until the very end
見てばかりいないで
Don't just keep watching
ひらりひらり嵐としていくならいい
Fluttering like a storm if you like
負けるのが怖い？ you're easy game
Are you afraid to lose? You're easy game
読み切って レッツ showdown
Reading it through, let's showdown
deal with the devil
見透かして あたしのものにする
See right through, make you all mine
あなたの髪の毛一本まで全部
Down to the very last hair on your head
a million dollars i'd say raise
震えてるわ坊や
Trembling, my boy
興奮たまらないわ スリル
Unstoppable excitement, the thrill
誰にも触らせない この money
No one can touch this money
a million dollars i'd say raise
さあ com'on
So come on
覚悟キメて
Make up your mind
ハイになるまで打って
Hit until we're high
報酬は入社後平行線で
My pay since joining the company has been flat
東京は愛せど何もない
I love Tokyo, but there's nothing here
リッケン620頂戴
Please give me a Rickenbacker 620
19万も持って居ない 御茶の水
I don't even have 190,000 yen, Ochanomizu
マーシャルの匂いで飛んじゃって大変さ
The scent of a Marshall makes me soar, it's serious
毎晩絶頂に達しているだけ
I'm just reaching the peak every night
ラット1つを商売道具にしているさ
I've made one Rat my trade tool
そうしたらベンジが肺に映ってトリップ
And then Benji is reflected in my lungs, taking a trip
最近は銀座で警察ごっこ
Recently playing cops and robbers in Ginza
国境は越えても盛者必衰
Even crossing borders, the prosperous must decline
領収書を書いて頂戴
Please write me a receipt
税理士なんて就いて居ない 後楽園
There's no tax accountant hired, Korakuen
将来僧になって結婚して欲しい
In the future, I want you to become a monk and marry me
毎晩寝具で遊戯するだけ
Just playing in our bedding every night
ピザ屋の彼女になってみたい
I want to try being a pizzeria girl
そうしたらベンジ、あたしをグレッチで殴って
And then Benji, beat me with your Gretsch
青漬けいて熟れて頂戴
Please let me ripen...
報酬は入社後平行線で
Pay runs flat ever since I was hired,
東京は愛せど何もない
I love Tokyo, but there's nothing here.
リッケン620頂戴
Won't you buy me a Rickenbacker 620?
19万も持っていない 御茶の水
I don't even have 190k, Ochanomizu.
マーシャルの匂いで飛んじまって大変さ
Tripping out on Marshall's scent is tough,
毎晩絶頂に達しているだけ
I'm just reaching climax every night.
ラット1つを商売道具にしているさ
Using a single RAT pedal as my trade tool,
そしたらベンジーが肺に映ってトリップ
Then Benzie is reflected in my lungs, tripping out.
最近は銀座で警察ごっこ
Lately it's playing cops and robbers in Ginza,
国境は越えても盛者必衰
Even crossing borders, the mighty must fall.
領収書を書いて頂戴
Write me up a receipt, won't you?
税理士なんて就いていない 後楽園
No tax accountants hired in Kourakuen.
将来僧になって結婚して欲しい
I want you to become a monk and marry me,
毎晩寝具で遊戯するだけ
Just playing games in our bedding every night.
ピザ屋の彼女になってみたい
I want to try becoming a pizza girl,
そしたらベンジー、あたしをグレッチで殴って
Then Benzie, hit me with your Gretsch!
あおいなら甘噛んで頂戴
Give me a soft bite if it's Ao,
終電で戻ってりゃ 池袋
Catching the last train back to Ikebukuro.
マーシャルの匂いで飛んじまって大変さ
Tripping out on Marshall's scent is tough,
毎晩絶頂に達しているだけ
I'm just reaching climax every night.
ラット1つを商売道具にしているさ
Using a single RAT pedal as my trade tool,
そしたらベンジーが肺に映ってトリップ
Then Benzie is reflected in my lungs, tripping out.
将来僧になって結婚して欲しい
I want you to become a monk and marry me,
毎晩寝具で遊戯するだけ
Just playing games in our bedding every night.
ピザ屋の彼女になってみたい
I want to try becoming a pizza girl,
そしたらベンジー、あたしをグレッチで殴って
Then Benzie, hit me with your Gretsch!
あおいなら甘噛んで頂戴
Give me a soft bite if it's Ao,
終電で戻ってりゃ 池袋
Catching the last train back to Ikebukuro.
マーシャルの匂いで飛んじまって大変さ
Tripping out on Marshall's scent is tough,
毎晩絶頂に達しているだけ
I'm just reaching climax every night.
ラット1つを商売道具にしているさ
Using a single RAT pedal as my trade tool,
そしたらベンジーが肺に映ってトリップ
Then Benzie is reflected in my lungs, tripping out.
今日も元気にドカンをきめたら
Today too, looking sharp with my sukeban pants,
ヨウラン背負ってリーゼント
Rocking a pompadour with my floral embroidery jacket!
ツッパリ High School Rock'n Roll
Tsuppari High School Rock'n Roll!
ソリも入れたし弁当も持ったし
Got my shaved eyebrows and packed my lunch box too,
可愛いあの娘はくるくるパーマに
That cute girl has a curly perm,
長めのスカートひきずって
Dragging her extra-long skirt behind her!
ツッパリ High School Rock'n Roll
Tsuppari High School Rock'n Roll!
お手手つないで駅までしあわせ
Holding hands all the way to the station in pure bliss,
駅に着いたらとっぴなお兄ちゃんと
Once we reached the station, ran into some flashy big bro,
ガンのくれあいとばしあい
Giving each other hard stares and picking a fight!
ツッパリ High School Rock'n Roll
Tsuppari High School Rock'n Roll!
タイマンはりましょアガテプ同士で
Let's have a solo fight as fellow punks!
かあちゃん、そんなに心配すんなよ
"Mom, don't worry so much about me."
勉強きらいな俺だけどさ
"I might hate studying, but y'know,"
人にはそれぞれあった道ってもんがあるんだよ
"Everyone's got their own path in life."
もっとやさしく大きな愛でひ弱い僕を包んでほしいなァ
"I want you to wrap weak little me in a bigger, gentler love."
なんだよtaku あそこにかぶい女いるじゃんよ
"What is it, Taku? There's a flashy girl over there."
ダセー 男つれてんな おいジョニーじゃない
"Lame. She's with some guy—wait, isn't that Johnny?!"
電車に乗ったら便所にかけ込み
Once on the train, dashing straight to the restroom,
一駅だけの happy time
A one-station-long happy time!
ツッパリ High School Rock'n Roll
Tsuppari High School Rock'n Roll!
火のないところに煙を立てて
Stirring up smoke where there's no fire,
電車を飛び降り改札抜けたら
Jumping off the train and rushing through the ticket gates,
学校までは猛ダッシュ
Running full speed all the way to school!
ツッパリ High School Rock'n Roll
Tsuppari High School Rock'n Roll!
またまた遅刻で今日も呼び出し
Late once again, called out to the teacher's office today too!
ツッパリ High School Rock'n Roll
Tsuppari High School Rock'n Roll!
バレル！
Exposed!
Ooh yeah ちょっと待って何これ知らぬ間に曲がって
Ooh yeah, wait, what is this, curving before I even knew it
Ooh yeah どこにも見当たらない人の足跡へ
Ooh yeah, toward human footprints nowhere to be found
胸の波打ち際抑え送り込む肺に酸素また増え
Pressing the chest's shore, pumping more oxygen into the lungs
灰色の酸素気候 愛のヤキイモ
Gray oxygen climate, love's baked sweet potato
Who's next?
次は何が湧き出すか奇跡的な違いぞ
What's welling up next? A miraculous difference
薄っぺらのしがらみにかきわけ誰もがちゃまらご
Pushing through thin shackles, everyone's a mess
上も下も知ったこっちゃないパンパンな巻き気味な力から水平ごと
Not caring about top or bottom, swollen winding power from the horizontal
現れ見せ付けるとくと味わいたけりゃ
Appearing and showing off, if you want to taste it fully
滑り出したあのオーバーレブ
That slipping over-rev
ジャムらんず遠く遠くまで
Jamming not, far, far away
白線の内側へ阿吽千選連の呼び声
Inside the white line, the call of a thousand selections
Ooh yeah えげつないもんを発見したのかも
Ooh yeah, maybe we discovered something vicious
生中継革命前夜換気扇越しのラボバレる
Live broadcast, eve of revolution, lab exposed through the fan
ほら俺の全部の才能がバレる
Look, all my talent is exposed
マジこれめんどくさいなバレる
Seriously, this is a pain, it's exposed
バレる 夜の仲間に気付かれる
Exposed... Noticed by the companions of the night
Let's get it. ほら、like a game, oh my, Haters 独り占め巣はビレッジ
Let's get it. Come on, like a game, oh my, Haters monopolizing the village nest
ほれ見なよ、こんなにかっこいいやろ?
Hey look, aren't I so cool?
Ooh yeah 拍手と歓声 ここ日が当たる場所
Ooh yeah, applause and cheers, this is the place where the sun shines
冷静沈着に足つけたままありがとう
Staying calm and composed with feet on the ground, thank you
知名度も名声も水物勝ち負けも雀の涙航海で頭で分かっちゃいる癖に
Fame and reputation are fleeting, wins and losses are minor, knowing it in my head...
身体が真っ二つミスたりあ
My body splits in two, Mysteria
はるか小国に群がる錆び 栄華を貪る一人ゲームから一度のミスが命取り
Rust swarming a distant small country, devouring glory, from a solo game a single mistake is fatal
一斉に白黒つけれないもう捨てもじゃいられない
Can't sort black and white all at once, can't throw it away anymore either
やばい失うものが惜しい欲しい欲しい欲しい
Shit, what I'll lose is precious, I want it, want it, want it!
俺を分かってくれと叫ぶように知らしめたばかりに
Just because I made them know, crying out for them to understand me
自分で自分をより自分らしく演じなきゃいけないはまり
Trapped in having to act more like myself by myself
求められてるあの味でも俺はもうそこにない俺って誰俺って何ビビって手も足も出ないで
Even with the taste they want, I'm no longer there. Who am I? What am I? Trembling, hands and feet won't move
される... 俺にはもう何もない
Exposed... I have nothing left
やばい そもそも勘違いだった
Shit, it was a misunderstanding to begin with
バレる... ボケの皮は剥がされる Let's get it.
Exposed... The skin of the dummy is peeled off. Let's get it.
ほら、like a game, oh my, Haters
Come on, like a game, oh my, Haters
手を叩いて指さしてほれ見なよかっこいいだろ笑える
Clap your hands, point your fingers, hey look, isn't it cool? It's laughable
生き延びる限りは価値に逃げできねんな衰え錆びつきとかされてしまうさだめか
As long as you survive, you can't run from value; is it fate to wither and rust away?
目をはいだのは寝起きを描いたのはあの日の俺とよく似た目をした奴でした
The one who peeled off eyes, the one who painted waking up, was someone with eyes just like me that day
あいにく俺はまだ渡らぬ三途の川は今日もまた積み上げては吹き飛ばされるサイクロラ
Unfortunately, I still haven't crossed the Sanzu River; today too, the roller piles up and gets blown away
痛み顔飽きたい ニヤリと微笑んだ
Tired of the painful face, smiled a grin
きっとこの腰をのばすような刀と大人しく
Surely, a sword that stretches this waist and obediently...
バレる... ほら俺の全部の才能が
Exposed... Look, all my talent is...
バレる... マジこれめんどくさいな
Exposed... Seriously, this is a pain
バレる... 夜の仲間に気付かれる Let's get it.
Exposed... Noticed by companions of the night. Let's get it.
ほら、like a game, oh my, Haters 独り占め巣はビレッジ ほれ見なよ、こんなにかっこいいやろ笑える
Come on, like a game, oh my, Haters monopolizing the village nest. Hey look, aren't I so cool? It's laughable
こんちくわ
Hello there!
とどきはしめ はじめ
Todoroki Hajime!
こんちくわ
Hello there!
泣いちゃうぞ ぴゃん ぴゃん
I'm gonna cry! Pyan pyan!
うーん すきや
Hmm... I love you!
泣いちゃうぞ ぴゃん ぴゃん 泣いちゃうぞ
I'm gonna cry! Pyan pyan! I'm gonna cry!
ごめん
Sorry!
最終手段 抱いてやる
Ultimate measure: I'll hold you!
こんちくわ こんちくわ
Konchikuwa! Konchikuwa!
ぴゃ！ぴゃ！ぴゃ！ぴゃ！
Pyat! Pyat! Pyat! Pyat!
カッオてき 仮想敵？
Katsuo-teki? Imaginary enemy?
ぴゃ！ぴゃ！ぴゃ！ぴゃ！
Pyat! Pyat! Pyat! Pyat!
泣かれたら 泣き返す 今を生きてよ やさしいじゃん
If you cry, I'll cry back. Live in the present, you're so nice!
抱くか
Hold you?
こんちくわ こんちくわ
Konchikuwa! Konchikuwa!
終わり わお！
The end! Wow!
あのノエル先輩がね
You know, Noelle-senpai...
ラップしてたんよなちょっと対抗してみようかな
Was rapping. Maybe I'll try competing with her.
もうちょっと諦めない気がするけど頭真ん中で
Feels like I shouldn't give up yet, right in my head...
よーし これでいこう!
Alright, let's do this!
二日目！
Day two!
ノエルだんちょーに対抗！
Taking on Noel-dancho!
うちらっぷぱんちょー！
Uchiha rap banchou!
ラップでバトルしよーよ！
Let's do a rap battle!
うちらっぷぱんちょー！
Uchiha rap banchou!
初テーマはぶんぶんぱんちょー！
First theme is Bum-bum-banchou!
初レイドであっけなく終了！チキチキ！
First raid and it's over already? Chiki-chiki!
その次テーマしたのはチキチキ！アルゲンなんだよー！
The next theme is... Chiki-chiki! Argen-nanda yo!
トワさんとフブキさんで大冒険だYO！
With Towa-san and Fubuki-san, it's a grand adventure, yo!
ビーバー特攻、セメントとタイジュ、大成功で終わったYO！
Beaver Tokko, cement and taiju, big success, it's over, yo!
もっと強くなるぱんちょー！ういやー！
Getting even stronger, banchou! Wryaa!
あ！おい！ノエルお前負けてんぞ！
Oi, oi! Noel, you're a beginner, zo!
時間なさすぎてラップできなかった短物だよ！はははは！
There's no time, so you couldn't rap and you're short, yo! Haha!
チキチキ！
Chiki-chiki!
おい危ない！やめてよ日記でラップバトル始めないでよ全然いいけど！
Oi, that's dangerous! Stop it, Nikki! I didn't start a rap battle yet, though it's totally fine!
ラップバトル者かね！
Rap battle showdown, huh!
二日目！
Day two!
ノエルだんちょーに対抗！
Taking on Noel-dancho!
うちらっぷぱんちょー！
Uchiha rap banchou!
ラップでバトルしよーよ！
Let's do a rap battle!
うちらっぷぱんちょー！
Uchiha rap banchou!
初テーマはぶんぶんぱんちょー！
First theme is Bum-bum-banchou!
初レイドであっけなく終了！チキチキ！
First raid and it's over already? Chiki-chiki!
その次テーマしたのはチキチキ！アルゲンなんだよー！
The next theme is... Chiki-chiki! Argen-nanda yo!
トワさんとフブキさんで大冒険だYO！
With Towa-san and Fubuki-san, it's a grand adventure, yo!
ビーバー特攻、セメントとタイジュ、大成功で終わったYO！
Beaver Tokko, cement and taiju, big success, it's over, yo!
もっと強くなるぱんちょー！はい！
Getting even stronger, banchou! Hai!
番長の勝利、おめでとう！
Banchou wins, congratulations!
チキチキ！
Chiki-chiki!
I'm Koseki Bijou! アイム 礒崎はじめ！
I'm Koseki Bijou! I'm Isaki Hajime!
Boom Boom Boom! オッケー！
Boom Boom Boom! Okay!
はじめまして！きょうはいっしょにうたうー！
Hajimemashite! Today let's sing together!
うたうー！Let's go!
Let's sing! Let's go!
Cool! Yeah! Thank you, thank you!
アイム ばんちょー Yeah!
I'm Banchou! Yeah!
We were cool, right? We were cool, okey?
We were cool, right? We were cool, okay?
Very very happy! Thank you!
Can you say something for me?
Sticking out your gyatt for Nerizzler!
You're so Bau Bau! Ok, You're so...
You're so Biboo tax!
I just wanna be your Shiori! Yay! She said the thing!
Sticking out your gyatt for Nerizzler!
You're so Bau Bau! You're so Biboo tax!
I just wanna be your Shiori!
This one! Wow wow!
Are you ready? Okey!
Are you ready? Okay!
Cool! Yeah!
Thank you, thank you!
アイム ばんちょー Yeah!
I'm Banchou! Yeah!
We were cool, right? We were cool, okey?
Very very happy! Thank you!
I want to hear the word, Bijou senpai's "Ryourya."
はい??
Hai??
だまいちぇよもう、ぼよぼよ！
Damaicchi yo mou, bojobojo!
いまフワモコがぱんちょー先生の所に向かってます！オーバー！
Ima Fuwamoco wa banchou-sensei no tokoro ni mukattemasu! Obaa!
ぱんちょー先生だはじめ！
Banchou-sensei da hajime!
ぱんちょー先生、いま持ってまーす、持たれてまーしゅ！
Banchou-sensei, ima mottemasu, motaretemasu!
つめーたい！がまんしてね！
Tsume-tai! Gaman shite ne!
わ！つめーたい！おへそにつめーたい！
Wa! Tsume-tai! Oheso ni tsume-tai!
OK じゃあ！次わ... ハートマッサージね！
Okey, jaa! Tsugi wa... heart massage ne!
ハートマッサージ！マッサージぴえ！
Heart massage! Massage!
大丈夫！足いるよ？ I believe you!
Daijoubu! Ashi iryo? I believe you!
BAU BAU! ソーセージ！
BAU BAU! Sausage!
あたまがいたいよ、ぜんぶ大丈夫になるからね！
Atama ga itai yo, zenbu daijoubu ni naru kara ne!
これで大丈夫、げんきになったぁ！
Kore de daijoubu, genki ni nattaa!
これからも病院がんばろうね！うん、がんばろうね！
Kore kara mo byouin ganbarou ne! Un, ganbarou ne!
殴り合いましょか？
Naguriai mashu ka?
溜まってるわ、やめてw！
Tamatteru wa, yamete w!
まあ久しぶりにやるからね、ちょっとできるか。イクゾッ！
まあ久しぶりにやるからね、ちょっとできるか。 Ikuzo!
ドドドド... イヤーッ！
Dododo... Iyya!
負けねえ！ちけちけ！
Makenee! Chike-chike!
勝っ！やめーる！
Katte! Yamero!
やめてー！
Stop it!
オレの勝ち！
My win!
完全勝利！
Total victory!
ボール持ってモチュッ
Holding the ball, mochut...
Yes, I do.
ぶんぶんぶん ばんちょー！
Zoom zoom zoom, the bancho!
須多夜気 初めです またの名を ただの甘え坊だ
I'm Sudo Yaki Hajime. Also known as a total spoiled brat.
白銀ノエル またの名を牛丼太郎だ よろしくな！
Shirogane Noel, also known as Gyudon Taro. Nice to meet you!
イヤーッ！
Yikes!
負けられねえ
I won't lose!
オレの勝ち！
My win!
完全勝利！
Total victory!
なんだこのゲーム！気合いじゃどうにもならなかったか
What is this game?! Guess sheer willpower wasn't enough!
どうも ぷるでちおです
Hello, I'm Purudechio.
ぷるでち様様に負けたので 今からぷるでち様考案のうんちぷりぷりだんすをします
Since I lost to Lord Purudechi, I will now perform Lord Purudechi's devised Poop Poop Dance!
うんちゃ ぷりゃぷりゃ うんちゃ ぷりゃぷりゃ
Un-cha, purya purya, un-cha, purya purya
異界の扉 開かれ中 から来た 須多夜気初め
Sudo Yaki Hajime, who came from the opening door of another world!
またの名を 端々初め よろしくな！
Also known as Hashi-Hashi Hajime. Nice to meet you!
悪魔中から来た でびでびでびる またの名を うんちうんちうんち
Debidebitest, who came from the demon realm, also known as Poop Poop Poop!
うんち うんち うんち うんち王！
Poop, poop, poop, King of Poop!
はじめまして 来てくれてありがとう
Nice to meet you. Thank you for coming.
じゃあ今度僕が踊ってって言ったら踊ってくれる？
So if I ask you to dance later, will you dance?
うんちゃ ぷりゃぷりゃ うんちゃ ぷりゃぷりゃ
Un-cha, purya purya, un-cha, purya purya
またね また今度来てね
See you later. Come again next time.
また遊んでやるよ
I'll play with you again.
やったー！ せーのっ おつもるでちおー
Yay! Ready, set, Otsumorudechio!
ああ すごい楽しいコラボだった
Ah, that was such a fun collab!
ええと 神田ちゃん こっちこっち やあ すごい楽しかった
Um, Kanda-chan, over here, over here! Wow, it was so much fun!
あと 記念日も 12入札という ことなんですかね ありがとう！
And also, isn't it also the 12th anniversary or something? Thank you!
え デグロッチの皆と え ベちゃん！
Um, everyone from Degurochi, and Be-chan!
寺蔵先輩と 美優先輩と ふうあもこ先輩と 野乃原先輩と でびちゃん！
Te-kora-senpai, Miyu-senpai, Fuamoko-senpai, Nonohara-senpai, and Debi-chan!
というね 豪華10名のゲストが 来てくれてました うれしい！
Ten gorgeous guests came to visit us. I'm so happy!
あの 最後のね やっちょうは 初めのやる気出ないションを作ってくれた おだまよちゃんちゃん！
Also, that last song was made by Odamayo-chanchan, who created my unmotivated song!
かわいいメドレーありがとうございます
Thank you for the cute medley.
はい ということで ええと 皆さん どうでしか おちんちこじって言うな
Right, so um, everyone, how is it—don't say "pulling penises"!
ま でもね ちょっと ちょっと これから また 男子を指導したいので
But you know, since I want to mentor the boys from now on...
ちょっと待ってて ちょっと待ってて
Please wait a moment, please wait a moment.
疲れ 肩くたなってきたわ 伸びた伸びた
I'm getting tired and stiff. I stretched and stretched.
ということでね 次の曲に行きたいと思います 聞いてください
So, I'd like to move on to the next song. Please listen.
ワールドイズマイン
World Is Mine
世界で 一番お姫様
The number one princess in the world!
ワールドイズマイン
World is Mine
世界で一番おひめさま
The number one princess in the world,
そう言う扱い心得てよね
so make sure you know how to treat me.
その一 いつもと違う髪型に気付くこと
First thing, notice when I have a different hairstyle.
その二 ちゃんと靴まで見ること いいね?
Second thing, check my shoes too, okay?
その三 わたしの一言には 三つの言葉で返事すること
Third thing, reply to every word I say with three words.
わかったら 右手がお留守なのをなんとかして!
If you understand, do something about my empty right hand!
べつに わがままなんて言ってないんだから
It's not like I'm being selfish.
キミに心から思って欲しいの かわいいって
I just want you to truly think I'm cute.
世界で一番おひめさま
The number one princess in the world,
気がついて ねぇねぇ 待たせるなんて論外よ
realize that! Hey, keeping me waiting is out of the question!
わたしを誰だと思ってるの?
Who do you think I am?
もう なんだか あまいものが食べたい!
I want something sweet right now!
いま すぐにね イエー ヘイ ベイビー
Yeah! Hey, baby!
欠点? かわいいの間違いでしょ 文句は許しませんの
Flaws? You must mean cute, I won't allow complaints.
あのね、わたしの話ちゃんと聞いてる? ちょっと...
Hey, are you actually listening to what I'm saying? Listen up!
あ、それとね 白いおおかまさん 決まってるでしょ? 迎えに来て
Oh, and a white horse, you know? Come pick me up.
わかったら かしずいて 手を取って 「おひめさま」って
If you understand, take my hand and call me "princess".
べつに わがままなんて言ってないんだから
It's not like I'm being selfish,
でもね 少しっくらい叱ってくれたっていいのよ
but it's okay to scold me a little.
世界でわたしだけのおうじさま
My one and only prince in the world,
気がついて ほらほら お手々が空いてます ムクチで
realize that, our hands are empty, look.
無愛想なおうじさま もうどうして! 気がついてよ 早く
Reticent and blunt prince, why won't you just notice?
絶対 キミはわかってない! わかってないわ...
You definitely don't get it at all!
イエーイエー
Yeah!
いちごののったショートケーキ
Shortcake with a strawberry,
こだわりたまごのとろけるプリン
pudding made with fine eggs.
みんな みんな 我慢します わがままな子だと思わないで
I'm holding back on all of it, don't think I'm a selfish girl.
わたしだってやればできるもん あとで後悔するわ
Even I can do it if I try, you'll regret it later.
当然です! だってわたしは
Of course, because I am...
世界で一番おひめさま
The number one princess in the world,
ちゃんと見ててよね どこかに行っちゃうよ?
watch me closely, or I might go somewhere.
ふいに 抱きしめられた 急にそんな! え? 「怪我される危ないよ」そう言ってそっぽ向くキミ
Suddenly I was held tightly, "It's dangerous," you said, turning away.
...こっちが危ないわよ
...I think you're the one who's dangerous.
イエー ヘイ ベイビー
Yeah, hey, baby!
恋はイリューショソ 少しロマンティック
Love is an illusion, a bit romantic.
予想できないトリック仕掛けて
Playing tricks you wouldn't expect.
恋はイリューショソ 少しファンタスティック
Love is an illusion, a bit fantastic.
隠しきれないこの胸のドキドキ
My heart is beating too fast to hide.
瞳 閉じてみたらなの シュワ デュワ デュワ デュワ
If you close your eyes, you'll hear it go...
Get ready to play danger game
ああもう！ 本当イヤになるわ
Ah man! This is really getting annoying.
曇りのない無垢な瞳
Cloudless, innocent eyes,
(何映すのBaby)
(What are you reflecting, baby?)
ほらほらまたよそ見をしてる
Look, look, you're looking away again,
移り気な一途なフリのBad boy
fickle bad boy pretending to be devoted.
好きだよなんて言葉 簡単に行っちゃって
Saying "I love you" so easily,
(Why don’t we just stop having this shallow relationship?)
その気にさせといて 誰にでも優しくするのね
leading me on and being nice to everyone.
噂のアイツは 恋のイリュージョニスタ
That rumored guy is a love illusionist.
Fall in love with you 報われないの
Fall in love with you, unrequited,
胸を焦らす この気持ちは止められない
this burning feeling in my chest cannot be stopped.
理屈じゃないのよ
It's not about logic,
ただキミに 愛されるため
just to be loved by you.
作り上げた嘘の私が
Before my fabricated fake self
本当の恋を盗んでしまう前に
steals true love away,
(今) キミの心捕まえてみせる
(Now) I'll try capturing your heart.
Catch and close to you
さあ Hands up そろそろお別れですか
So Hands up, is it almost time to say goodbye?
覚悟を (覚悟を) 決めてね (決めてね)
Make up your mind (make up your mind),
狙い定めた Hunter
hunter who locked on the target,
引き金を引いて 呼吸が止まる瞬間
pulling the trigger, the moment breathing stops.
触れてしまいそうなの 触れてはいけないの
About to touch, must not touch,
(Why don’t we just stop having this shallow relationship?)
涼しい顔をして 悪びれもせず焦らすキミは
keeping a cool face, teasing without a hint of guilt.
そう 恋のファンタジスタ
Yes, the love fantasist.
手錠をかけた 剥き出しの本能
Handcuffs on, raw instinct exposed,
想像より「女の子」してんの私
I'm acting more like a "girl" than you'd imagine.
が私じゃいられない 優しいテンテーション
I can't stay myself, sweet temptation,
よそ見できない ひとりじめして
can't look away, I want you all to myself.
触れてしまいそうなの 触れてはいけないの
About to touch, must not touch,
恋はイリュージョンのように 少しロマンティック
love is like an illusion, a bit romantic.
優しくしないで ふとしたぬくもり
Don't be so gentle, an unexpected warmth.
瞳閉じしてみたら
If I close my eyes,
シュワシュワシュワシュワシュワシュワ
fizz, fizz, fizz, fizz...
聞こえてくるでしょう
You can hear it, right?
シャンパンの泡のように
Like champagne bubbles,
シュワシュワシュワシュワシュワシュワ 弾けているでしょう
fizz, fizz, fizz... popping, right?
映画のワンシーンみたいに キュンとする
Like a scene from a movie, making my heart flutter,
仕草リサーチしても
even if I research your gestures.
あなたに出会った瞬間 全部曖昧
The moment I met you, everything became vague.
揺れてるピンクサファイヤ 言葉よりメチャメチャ
Swaying pink sapphire, much more than words.
メチャメチャより心で 通じ合っても
Even if we communicate heart-to-heart rather than words,
慣れないしずけさに 緊張しちゃうから
because I get nervous in unfamiliar silence.
微笑んでねそんなの 贅沢かしら
Smiling like that, is it asking too much?
恋はイリュージョン 甘いテンテーション
Love is illusion, sweet temptation,
よそ見できない ひとりじめして
can't look away, I want you all to myself.
触れてしまいそうなの 触れてはいけないの
About to touch, must not touch.
恋はイリュージョン 甘いテンテーション
Love is illusion, sweet temptation,
少しファンタスティック かっこしきれない
a little fantastic, can't keep looking cool.
こんな胸のドキドキ 瞳とじてみたら
This heart pounding in my chest, if I close my eyes,
シュワシュワシュワシュワシュワシュワ 聞こえてくるでしょう
fizz, fizz, fizz... you can hear it, right?
シャンパンの泡のように シュワシュワシュワシュワシュワシュワ
Like champagne bubbles, fizz, fizz...
弾けているでしょう
popping, right?
恋はイリュージョン 甘いテンテーション
Love is illusion, sweet temptation,
よそ見できない ひとりじめして
can't look away, I want you all to myself.
触れてしまいそうなの 触れてはいけないの
About to touch, must not touch.
恋はイリュージョン 甘いテンテーション
Love is illusion, sweet temptation,
少しファンタスティック かっこしきれない
a little fantastic, can't keep looking cool.
こんな胸のドキドキ 瞳とじてみたら
This heart pounding in my chest, if I close my eyes,
シュワシュワシュワシュワシュワシュワ 聞こえてくるでしょう
fizz, fizz, fizz... you can hear it, right?
シャンパンの泡のように シュワシュワシュワシュワシュワシュワ
Like champagne bubbles, fizz, fizz...
弾けているでしょう
popping, right?
シャンパンの泡のように
Like champagne bubbles,
シュワシュワシュワシュワシュワシュワ 弾けているでしょう
fizz, fizz, fizz... popping, right?
恋はイリュージョン すごいロマンティック
Love is an illusion, super romantic.
優しすぎないで ふとしたぬくもり
Don't be too kind, an unexpected warmth.
瞳閉じしてみたら 胸が熱くなる
If I close my eyes, my chest gets hot.
恋はイリュージョン かなりファンタスティック
Love is an illusion, quite fantastic.
かっこしきれない こんな胸のドキドキ
Can't look cool, this heart pounding in my chest.
瞳とじてみたら シュワシュワシュワシュワシュワシュワ
If I close my eyes, fizz, fizz, fizz...
聞こえてくるでしょう シャンパンの泡のように
You can hear it, right? Like champagne bubbles.
シュワシュワシュワシュワシュワシュワ 弾けているでしょう
Fizz, fizz, fizz, fizz... popping, right?
いつまで子供のままでいる？
How long will you stay a child?
そんな言葉が降りかかる
Such words rain down upon me.
黙って見ていればいいんだ
Just stay quiet and watch,
笑ってそう言っていやれ
just laugh and say that.
人生にはないんだ Take 2
There is no take 2 in life,
平凡で腐らない退屈
ordinary, unspoiled boredom.
なんてごめんで現実的な言葉なんかに耳をふさげ
No thank you, plug your ears to realistic words.
ネバーランドに閉じこもって いつまでもだって夢を語るんだ
Shut yourself away in Neverland and talk of dreams forever.
笑う奴には唾を吐け
Spit on the ones who laugh,
どっちもこっちもいかないほ
neither this nor that works out.
綺麗事に踊り踊らされ
Dancing and being danced around by pretty words.
大人の言う常識なんてものは 丸めて捨てちまえ
Crumple up and throw away what adults call common sense.
ピーターパン症候群と 指をさされてのし上がれ
Rise up even if pointed at as Peter Pan syndrome.
おとぎ話みたいなハッピーエンドを 思い描いて生きていくんだ
Imagine a fairytale-like happy ending and live on.
あ…
Ah...
わぁ…
Woah...
いつまでも子どものままでいる？
"How long are you going to stay a child?"
そんな言葉がふりかかる
Those words are hurled at me.
黙ってみてれいんだ
"Just keep quiet and watch."
笑ってそういってやれ
"Laugh, that's what you should do."
好きに笑えよ
Laugh however you want!
それだけで別にいいさ
It doesn't matter anyway.
お前になんかに
To people like you...
お前らなんかに
何も言われたくない
I don't want to be told a thing.
黙ってみてろ！
Just shut up and watch!
やり直しのきかない人生
A life with no do-overs—
一度でいいチャンスをください
Give me one good chance!
掴んで離さない
I'll grab it and never let go.
もう俺のものなんだ
It's already mine!
ネバーランドの大気圏を破って
Breaking through the stratosphere of Neverland,
今夢をかなえるんだ
I'm going to make my dream come true right now!
笑う奴など蹴り飛ばせ
Blow away anyone who laughs!
打ち手はない残されてない？
"There are no moves left, you've got no options."
ネガティブを押し付けてくんな
Don't force your negativity on me!
大人のあいつも知らない世界を俺は生きてるんだ
I am truly living in a world...
ピーターパン症候群と
Even if they call it the Peter Pan Syndrome,
思われたって馬鹿にされたって
Even if they make a fool of me and mock me,
おとぎ話みたいなハッピーエンドに一直線に進んでいくんだ
I'll press forward straight toward a fairytale happy ending!
夢の見過ぎと馬鹿にされた少年が
The boy who was mocked as a dreamer...
夢を掴む物語を
is weaving a story of chasing dreams,
見事な逆転劇をこの手で巻き起こせ見せつけろ
and spinning a magnificent reversal with his own hands!
にっちもさっちもいかない？
"Is everything okay? Are you doing alright?"
綺麗事に踊り踊らされ
Dancing and being made to dance to high-sounding things,
大人の言う常識なんてものは丸めて捨てちまえ
just roll up adult conventional wisdom and throw it away!
ピーターパン症候群と
Peter Pan Syndrome—
指をさされ罵れようが
no matter how much they point fingers and hurl insults,
おとぎ話みたいなハッピーエンドをそう自ら掴み取るんだ
I'll seize a fairytale happy ending with my own two hands!
ねえ なん の タメ ガンバンノ
Hey, work hard for your own sake!
報われない day by day
Day by day, goes unrewarded.
結局 正直者が道化師で踊る残像
Afterall, honest folks are made fools of and dance to the afterglow.
狡賢く 生きてる あの子
That kid lives so cleverly,
懐 に 舞い込む 優等生 でしょ う
an honor student sneaking into the inner circle.
アブラカダブラ 開ける よ pandora
Abracadabra, open up, Pandora!
抑えきれない の さ 狂う カサインドラ
Can't hold it back anymore, a spinning kaleidoscope.
(Hey!)
six p.m. 鳴る alarm
6 p.m., the alarm rings.
暴れ馬で crew like a carnival
Run wild, my crew, like a carnival!
everybody gonna put your hand's clap clap
Everybody gonna put your hands up, clap, clap!
まだ見ぬ世界飛び込め 3.2.1
Dive into a world yet unseen, 3, 2, 1!
(doubt) i got it 壇上 へ
(Doubt!) Got it, onto the stage!
(doubt) 体 揺らし て
(Doubt!) Shake your body!
(doubt) ほら 既成概念 ある が まま ぶっ壊せ
(Doubt!) Come on, smash the status quo as it is!
(doubt) i got it 壇上 へ
(Doubt!) Got it, onto the stage!
(doubt) 体 揺らし て
(Doubt!) Shake your body!
(doubt) ほら 既成概念 ある が まま ぶっ壊せ
(Doubt!) Come on, smash the status quo as it is!
countach 最上級 の countach
Countach, top-tier Countach!
countach 一心不乱 で countach
Countach, single-minded Countach!
countach 陰 と 陽 の countach
Countach, light and shadow Countach!
countach 何度 だって countach
Countach, how many times, Countach!
息をひそめて自分を殺すのはもう慣れてるのさ
Holding my breath and killing myself—I'm already used to it.
存在価値 存在証明 なんてどうでもいいわ
Existence value, existence proof... who cares about that?
宴なら endless
If it's a feast, make it endless.
今宵取っ払うフェンス c'mon, borderless
Tonight, brush off the fences, c'mon, borderless!
滅紫の雷浴びて perfect
Bathed in dark-purple lightning, perfect!
弾き飛んで理性よ
Reason shatters and flies away!
アブラカダブラ 開ける よ pandora
Abracadabra, open up, Pandora!
抑えきれない の さ 狂う カサインドラ
Can't hold it back anymore, a spinning kaleidoscope.
本性 は カモフラージュ
My true nature is a camouflage,
本能 だけ で 十分 混ざり 合う
instinct alone is enough to mix together.
everybody gonna put your hand's clap clap
Everybody gonna put your hands up, clap, clap!
明日 の こと は 忘れろ 3.2.1
Forget about tomorrow, 3, 2, 1!
(doubt) 叫べ 天井 へ
(Doubt!) Shout to the heavens!
(doubt) 声 を 枯らし て
(Doubt!) Strain your voice!
ざらつくフロア
On the rough floor,
本能だけで十分混ざり合え
mix together with just instinct.
Everybody gonna put your hands up, up!
ぁ、そのことは忘れろ Switch on!
Ah, forget about that, switch on!
叫べテッペンへ
Shout toward the peak,
声をからして
until your voice is raspy.
君だけの人生 楽しまなきゃ損じゃん
It's a waste not to enjoy your own life!
叫べテッペンへ
Shout toward the peak,
声をからして
until your voice is raspy.
君だけの人生 楽しまなきゃ損じゃん
It's a waste not to enjoy your own life!
6PM鳴るアラーム
The 6 PM alarm rings,
暴れ馬で狂うべくカーニバル
a carnival to go wild like a runaway horse.
Everybody gonna put your hands up, up!
まだ見ぬ世界飛び込め Switch on!
Dive into a world you've never seen, switch on!
暴れ狂うダンスフロアへ
To the rampaging dance floor,
体揺らして
sway your body.
ホラ規制がない アルがままぶち壊せ
Hey, there are no regulations, smash it as it is!
暴れ狂うダンスフロアへ
To the rampaging dance floor,
体揺らして
sway your body.
ホラ規制がない アルがままぶち壊せ
Hey, there are no regulations, smash it as it is!
Countach 最上級のCountach
Countach, the top-tier Countach,
Countach 一身に浴びてCountach
Countach, bathe in it all at once, Countach.
イントロよりよろCountach
Yoroshiku more than the intro, Countach,
何度だってCountach
Countach, no matter how many times.
バンザイ 無能な命に
Banzai, to a useless life,
くだらないよ 偽物だってそれはラリアチュー
it's worthless, even if it's a fake, that's a lariat chu!
偶然息してるようなもん
Like something accidentally breathing,
不条理浴びながら僕はhome
I'm home while bathing in absurdity.
偶然息してるようなもん
Like something accidentally breathing,
不条理浴びながら僕はhome
I'm home while bathing in absurdity.
才能はゼロ
My talent is zero,
どうにかしちまっちゃんってるけど
though I've somehow gone crazy.
歓声はno だってばの
Cheers are a "no," I'm telling you.
愛にもたれた言葉で心拍数 生きてく程胸は沈んでゆく
Heart rate driven by sluggish words; the more I live, the more my chest sinks.
どうなってんだろ うな？
What's going on?
この音が揺れるの
This sound is shaking—
かいつまみでもしょうがねえ
well, even skimming through it can't be helped.
汗かき稼ぐお金はどんだけ？
How much money do I make sweating?
ああだこうだ
This and that,
そんなもんか
is that all it is?
五月蝿ぇわな
How annoying.
バンザイ 無能な命に
Banzai, to a useless life,
から回っていく脳を満たしてくれ
fill my spinning, empty brain.
未来予想図なんか描けない
I can't draw any future expectation map.
くだらないよ 偽物だってそれ
It's worthless, even if it's a fake, that's—
半端者ならやれない nutty tune
A nutty tune that half-hearted people can't pull off.
朱色になって僕は思い通り
Turning crimson, I am just as I want to be.
太陽系で蹲った
Crouching in the solar system,
罵詈雑言インベーダー
abasing abuse invader.
足が止まっているシューゲイザー
A shoegazer with stopped feet,
死にそうでもギリですか
is it barely okay even if I look like I'm dying?
のらりくらり交わすわ
I evade evasively.
初めましてカミサマ
Nice to meet you, God.
もし救われるのなら
If I'm going to be saved,
腹切るわ今から
I'll commit seppuku right now.
get down 揺らねくget down
get down, shaking get down,
飲み込んだ清濁が君を狂わせてんだ
the swallowed purity and impurity are driving you mad.
めったなもんじゃおどろかねえ
I won't be surprised by anything rare,
汗かき生いた最期もおっけねえ
and my sweaty final moments are fine too.
なんだかんだ
This and that,
そんなもんさ
that's how it is.
虚しいわな
How empty.
バンザイ 無能な命に
Banzai, to a useless life,
から回ってく脳を満たしてくれ
fill my spinning, empty brain.
未来予想図なんか描けない
I can't draw any future expectation map.
くだらないよ 偽物だってそれは
It's worthless, even if it's a fake, that's—
半端者ならやれない nutty tune
A nutty tune that half-hearted people can't pull off.
朱色になって僕は思い通り
Turning crimson, I am just as I want to be.
はい！ということでチェキ風グッズが出まーす！
So, some cheki-style merchandise is coming out!
轟はジ初めチェキ誕生記念2025フルセットはこんな感じです！
Todoroki Hajime's 1st Birthday Commemoration 2025 full set looks like this!
1つ目！アクリルパネル！おちちゃうちぇんの可愛いイラストと、こちらはオーロラな加工になってます！
First! Acrylic panel! With cute illustrations by Ochicha-chen, and it has an aurora finish!
2つ目！BANCHOアクリルキーホルダー！おもちちゃうちぇんの、ぶんぶんぶーん BANCHOのイラストです！
Second! BANCHO acrylic keychain! Featuring omochicha-chen's buzzing BANCHO illustration!
3つ繋げても1つずつでも使えます！カラビナは、イカヅチの形になってます！ぜひカバンとかにつけてみてね！
You can connect three or use them individually! Carabiners are shaped like lightning bolts! Be sure to attach them to your bag!
3つ目！BANCHOナイロンジャケット！こちらは、実際に出づぶちぇで色味をチェックして使いやすいデザインにしました！
Third! BANCHO nylon jacket! We actually checked the colors in person to make it an easy-to-use design!
おもちちゃうちぇんのミニBANCHOのイラストと、おもてには初めての考えたBANCHOのロゴがついてます！ジップは、イカヅチの形になってます！
With mini BANCHO illustrations by omochicha-chen and the first-ever BANCHO logo I designed on the front! The zipper is shaped like a lightning bolt!
キービジュアルの初めてと驚きのデザインです！最後！シチュエーションボイス！ナイロンジャケットにまつわるボイスです！
It's a design featuring the key visual's first-time theme and surprise! Last! Situation voice! It's a voice related to the nylon jacket!
よかったら合わせて聞いてください！今回フルセット購入特典は2つあります！
Please check it out together if you'd like! This time, there are two full set purchase bonuses!
1つ目！直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカード！エーエムシェーゲになってます！
First! Autographed cheki-style bromide card! It's an AM-shūge!
2つ目！ホロライブショップにて購入した方限定で、ホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームで使えるカードが1枚付きます！カードの詳細や遊び方については公式ホームページを見てください！
Second! Limited to those who purchase at the hololive shop, you'll get one card usable in the hololive Official Card Game! Check the official homepage for details on the card and how to play!
以上グッズ紹介でした！いいきっちゅあん！
That concludes the merchandise introduction! Good job, everyone!
あの、まだまだ踊っていくのでぜひ最後まで見てくださいね！ちょうちょ、いけ！はじめたんしゃきょく！
Um, we're still going to keep dancing, so please watch until the very end! Chōcho, let's go! Hajime's solo song!
ということでもなちゃん本当にありがとうございます！
So Mona-chan, thank you truly so much!
このあと21時新曲ばんざいMVプレミア公開！そしてグッズ販売も開始されます！
After this at 21:00, the premiere of the new song "Banzai" MV! And merchandise sales will also begin!
そしてそのあとはメンバー限定のアンコールライブもあります！
And after that, there's also a member-limited encore live!
時間ぴったり！うれちい！
Right on time! I'm so happy!
あのちょれんもね、ありがとうございます本当に！みんなちゃーんありがとうございます！みんなちゃーんありがとうございます！
Um, choren too, thank you so much! Really! Everyone, thank you so much! Everyone, thank you so much!
みなたん！！いつも応援ありがとう！！ずっと夢だった主役LIVEができて本当に幸せです！
Minatan!! Thank you always for your support!! I'm so happy to have the starring live I've always dreamed of!
次のステージではもっとパワーアップして、毎回最高を更新するから！！
On the next stage, I'll power up even more and keep outdoing myself every single time!!
FIRST STARRING ROLE TUDOROKI HAJIME BIRTHDAY LIVE 2025
重大告知
Major Announcement